# Andrew Banagas Web Developer

Phone #: (562) 325-2358

Address: 7509 Kengard Ave, Whittier, CA, 90606 LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/andrew-banagas/

GitHub: github.com/drew990 Portfolio: banagas.com

# **Objective**

I am a Full Stack Web Developer with a Certification of Completion from UC Berkeley's Coding Bootcamp and experience in Front-end web development. I am looking for a Software Developer position at an innovative company where I will be challenged to use my abilities, talents, and two years of experience to their full potential.

### **Work Experience**

Hadley Tow, Whittier - Battery Service Provider

Feb 2022 - Present

- Provide services to members such as installing batteries, changing tires, and unlocking cars so members can get their keys again
- Critically analyze the situation, as every car has its own unique features
- Tested batteries and gathered info to determine the results and the state of a battery
- Work with coworkers to provide backup if a member's car gets too hard for one person to work on

Windsor, Santa Fe Springs - Warehouse Material Handler

Dec 2021 - Jan 2022

- Responsible for separating units into the correct departments
- Communicated with coworkers to work as efficiently as possible
- Emailed back to departments about changes or about updated units in inventory

# **Project Section**

Joslyne Portfolio - github.com/drew990/joslyneportfolio

- Designed and developed the front-end of the website
- Developed using NextJS, GraphCMS, and Framer Motion
- The Web Application allows the user to continuously make updates to their website without needing a developer

### Yummy-Grocery - github.com/StephenWDickey/yummy-grocery

- Lead front-end developer and a member of four responsible for developing the web application
- Developed using React, Express, Graphql, Apollo, mongoose, stripe, etc.
- The web application was custom designed using Figma

#### **Education**

# Full Stack Web Developer Certificate (Completed in 2022)

UC Berkeley Coding Boot Camp

Technology Used: HTML, JavaScript, CSS, Express, Node.is, React, MySQL, Mongoose, ORM, OOP

# Applied Physics / California State University - San Marcos

April 2017 - March 2021 (Unfinish)